<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WeatherApp</string>
    <string name="icon_desc">Coba</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="min_temp_text">Min Temp: %1$d°C</string>
    <string name="max_temp_text">Max Temp: %1$d°C</string>
    <string name="time_item_forecast">Sekarang</string>
    <string name="celcius_item_forecast">10°C</string>

    <string name="titleHeatIndex">Heat Index</string>
    <string name="descHeatIndex">
        The heat index measures how hot it feels by combining air temperature and humidity. It reflects
        the "feels-like" temperature, as high humidity makes it harder for the body to cool down. This
        is important for understanding heat-related risks, especially in hot weather.
    </string>
    <string name="titleWindChill">Wind Chill</string>
    <string name="descWindChill">
        Wind chill is a measure of how cold it feels on the skin when wind speed is combined with 
        the air temperature. As the wind increases, it strips away body heat, making the air feel 
        colder than the actual temperature. Wind chill is important in cold weather, as it helps 
        indicate the risk of frostbite or hypothermia.
    </string>
    <string name="titleWind">Wind</string>
    <string name="descWind">
        Wind is the movement of air caused by the uneven heating of the Earths surface. It transfers heat,
        moisture, and particles, influencing weather and climate patterns.
    </string>
    <string name="titlePressure">Pressure</string>
    <string name="descPressure">
        Pressure is the force of air in the atmosphere. It affects weather, with high pressure bringing clear 
        skies and low pressure causing clouds and storms.
    </string>
    <string name="titleHumidity">Humidity</string>
    <string name="descHumidity">
        Humidity is the amount of moisture (water vapor) in the air. Higher humidity makes the air
        feel warmer, while lower humidity feels cooler and drier. It influences weather, comfort, and
        how we perceive temperature.
    </string>
    <string name="titleVisibility">Visibility</string>
    <string name="descVisibility">
        Visibility refers to the distance at which objects can be clearly seen. It is affected by
        weather conditions such as fog, rain, snow, and pollution. Low visibility can impact travel
        safety, particularly for driving and flying.
    </string>


    <string-array name="time_labels">
        <item>08:00</item>
        <item>12:00</item>
        <item>16:00</item>
        <item>20:00</item>
        <item>00:00</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="temperature_values">
        <item>20°C</item>
        <item>25°C</item>
        <item>22°C</item>
        <item>19°C</item>
        <item>18°C</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="weather_icons">
        <item>@drawable/cloud</item>
        <item>@drawable/cloud</item>
        <item>@drawable/cloud</item>
        <item>@drawable/cloud</item>
        <item>@drawable/cloud</item>
    </integer-array>
    <string name="appwidget_text">ForecastToday</string>
    <string name="add_widget">Add widget</string>
    <string name="app_widget_description">Weather For Today</string>

    <string name="feature_under_development">This feature is currently under development.</string>
    <string name="pricing_issue_message">I am facing pricing issues that prevent me from implementing this feature at this time.</string>
    <string name="feedback_button_text">Provide Feedback</string>
</resources>